unu.edu 2017-12-25

# Privacy Statement - United Nations University

* This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices of the United Nations University (UNU).

UNU is committed to the privacy of individuals who visit and interact with www.unu.edu and follows these practices.

**What personally-identifiable information does UNU collect on www.unu.edu and how does the organization use it?**

UNU may collect information from our users in various ways. UNU is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell or rent this information to others, or share it in any manner, in ways different from the practices disclosed in this statement.

**Log Files**

UNU uses the IP address from your Internet connection to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements and gather broad geographic information for aggregate use. The IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**Sharing**

UNU may share aggregated contact, demographic and other information with the various institutes and programmes of the UNU system. This information will not be shared with any other entity.

**Links**

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website. The UNU website contains links to other sites. Please note that UNU is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

**Notification of Changes**

UNU will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. If UNU decides to change its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this page so that our users are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by e-mail. Users will be given the choice as to whether or not to allow us to use their information in this different manner.
